<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>admin on E&amp;C Data Science Blog</title>
    <link>/authors/admin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in admin on E&amp;C Data Science Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2019</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/authors/admin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring US Demographics with data from the General Social Survey</title>
      <link>/post/gss-data-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/gss-data-project/</guid>
      <description>Research Proposal For this project I will research the racial differences and disparities in American economics, politics, and culture. I will use statistical analysis to look for correlations in these differences. The independent variable will be race and the dependent variables will be family income, political party, and average amount of TV somebody watches.
 The GSS Dataset The dataset is from the General Social Survey (GSS). It is a national survey conducted by NORC at the University of Chicago, to gather data on the complexity of American life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploratory Data Analysis with Diamonds</title>
      <link>/post/eda-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/eda-project/</guid>
      <description>For this post I decided to walk through the steps of exploratory data analysis using the diamonds dataset that come with base R.
Plotting the Data data(&amp;#39;diamonds&amp;#39;) #Loading the dataset summary(diamonds) #Looking at the summary of the dataset ## carat cut color clarity ## Min. :0.2000 Fair : 1610 D: 6775 SI1 :13065 ## 1st Qu.:0.4000 Good : 4906 E: 9797 VS2 :12258 ## Median :0.7000 Very Good:12082 F: 9542 SI2 : 9194 ## Mean :0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/author/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/author/admin/</guid>
      <description>I am an undergraduate student at Emory University. I am currently a Technology Consultant at Emory&amp;rsquo;s Cox Computing Center. Data Analytics is my passion, and R programming is my bread and butter. I am interested in Econometrics, Data Privacy, and Business Intelligence. I believe we are in the midst of a data revolution that will define our future, meaning that we have the responsibility to shape what that future looks like through responsible data practices.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>